gamepapa.com 2014-04-21

# Play at Gamepapa.com Free Online games arcade site

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR Gamepapa.COM**  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate Gamepapa.com commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Any personal information that you provide to Gamepapa.com shall stay absolutely safe, private and secure. We **DO NOT** share or resell personal information to outside sources.

 **INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED**  
Gamepapa.com **DOES NOT** log any information about you, your computer, your internet service provider or your internet connection.

 **COOKIES**  
Gamepapa.com **DOES NOT** use cookies to store information about your visits. However, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

 **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**  
Gamepapa.com use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click Here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

 **EXTERNAL LINKS**  
Gamepapa.com contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **CONTACTING OUR WEB SITE**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can [contact us.](http://www.gamepapa.com/play/support)
